[
  {
    "Year": 2011,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Digital subscriber line",
    "Connections": 1034000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2011,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Cellular, satellite, cable and fixed wireless",
    "Connections": 413000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2011,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Fibre optic",
    "Connections": 3700
  },
  {
    "Year": 2012,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Digital subscriber line",
    "Connections": 1131000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2012,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Cellular, satellite, cable and fixed wireless",
    "Connections": 479000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2012,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Fibre optic",
    "Connections": 5400
  },
  {
    "Year": 2013,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Digital subscriber line",
    "Connections": 1189000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2013,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Cellular, satellite, cable and fixed wireless",
    "Connections": 570000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2013,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Fibre optic",
    "Connections": 13000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2014,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Digital subscriber line",
    "Connections": 1321000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2014,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Cellular, satellite, cable and fixed wireless",
    "Connections": 550000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2014,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Fibre optic",
    "Connections": 46000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2015,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Digital subscriber line",
    "Connections": 1335000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2015,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Cellular, satellite, cable and fixed wireless",
    "Connections": 485000
  },
  {
    "Year": 2015,
    "Question": "Broadband Internet connections",
    "Response": "Fibre optic",
    "Connections": 105000
  }
]